<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Andres Garcia-Saavedra</title>
    <link>/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Andres Garcia-Saavedra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic</title>
      <link>/home/hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/hero/</guid>
      <description>The highly flexible website framework for Hugo with an extensible plugin mechanism. Create a beautifully simple site in under 10 minutes 🚀 Latest release  
(function defer() { if (window.jQuery) { jQuery(document).ready(function(){ GetLatestReleaseInfo(); }); } else { setTimeout(function() { defer() }, 50); } })(); function GetLatestReleaseInfo() { $.getJSON(&#39;https://api.github.com/repos/gcushen/hugo-academic/tags&#39;).done(function (json) { let release = json[0]; // let downloadURL = release.zipball_url; $(&#39;#academic-release&#39;).text(&#39;Latest release &#39; + release.name); }); }  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Biography Andres Garcia-Saavedra is a Principal Research Scientist at NEC Laboratories Europe, Germany. His research interests lie in the application of fundamental mathematics to real-life computer communications systems, both wired and (specially) wireless; including resource allocation problems, energy efficiency, network coding, low-delay communications and Tactile Internet applications (haptic VR/AR). He particularly enjoys building real prototypes and carrying out experimental performance evaluations of protocols and communication systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>/home/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/talks/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Publications</title>
      <link>/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected Publications</title>
      <link>/home/publications_selected/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/publications_selected/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Projects</title>
      <link>/home/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/posts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service to Research Community</title>
      <link>/home/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/community/</guid>
      <description>Editorial and Organization duties  [2025-] Technical Program Commitee (TPC) member of ACM MobiSys [2025-] Technical Program Commitee (TPC) member of ACM CoNEXT [2025-] Technical Program Commitee (TPC) member of IEEE INFOCOM [2024-] Area Editor of IEEE Transactions on Wireless Communications [2024-] Associate Editor of IEEE Transactions on Mobile Computing [2023] Local Chair ACM MobiCom 2023, Madrid [2021-2024] Associate Editor of IEEE Transactions on Network Science and Engineering [2020] Local Chair IEEE ICNP 2020, Madrid [2018] Technical Program Commitee (TPC) Chair ACM WiNTECH 2018 [2016-now] Area Editor of Elsevier Computer Communications [2016] Technical Program Commitee (TPC) Chair IEEE Online GreenComm 2016 [2013] Web and Software Tools Chair IEEE Online GreenComm 2013  Other Technical Program Committee (TPC) and reviewing duties  TPC member in IEEE Globecom (2018, 2019), MadCom (2018), FiCloud (2018), IEEE COMNETSAT (2018), IEEE MASS (2018), EFC-IoT (2018), IEEE VTC (2015-Fall, 2017-spring), Elsevier Computer Communications (2014, 2015, 2016), MACOM (2014, 2015), AWICT (2015), IEEE GlobalSIP (2015), MOBIWAC (2014, 2015, 2016, 2017, 2018), ACM WiNTECH (2013, 2016, 2017, 2019), SustainIT (2013, 2014, 2015, 2016), ICALP (2012) Regular reviewer of IEEE Communication Letters (2014 Exemplary Reviewer), IEEE Journal on Selected Areas in Communication (JSAC), IEEE Transactions on Vehicular Technology, IEEE INFOCOM, IEEE Wireless Communications, IEEE/ACM Transactions on Networking, IEEE Transactions on Mobile Computing, IEEE Communications Magazine, IEEE Transactions on Communications, IEEE Transactions on Wireless Communications, IEEE Communication Surveys &amp;amp; Tutorials, IEEE Globecom, IEEE VTC, Elsevier Adhoc Networks, Springer Wireless Networks, International Conference on Communications (ICT), EURASIP Journal on Wireless Communications and Networking, IEEE Globecom, International Workshop on Multiple Access Communications (MACOM), Elsevier Computer Communications (COMCOM), Elsevier Computer Networks (COMNET), International Symposium on Personal, Indoor and Mobile Radio Communications (PIMRC), International Workshop on Wireless Network Testbeds (WiNTECH), International Colloquium on Automata, Languages and Programming (ICALP), International Symposium on a World of Wireless, Mobile and Multimedia Networks (IEEE WoWMoM).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>/home/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Student supervision  Marco Rossanese, Ph.D. Informatik, Technische Universität Darmstadt (2024). Josep Xavier Salvat, M.Sc. Telematics Eng., Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya (2016), Ph.D., University of Kaiserslautern (2018) Jose Maria Montes Yuste, B.Sc. Telematics Eng., University Carlos III of Madrid (2013). Georgios Z. Papadopoulos, M.Sc Telematics Eng., University Carlos III of Madrid (2012). Vasileios Papadopoulos, B.Sc. Software Eng., Alexander Technological Institute of Thessaloniki (2011).  Courses  Mathematics for telecommunications (19 /20, 20 /21, 21 /22, 22 /23): BSc course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tags</title>
      <link>/home/tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/tags/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/home/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>