<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Andres Garcia-Saavedra</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Andres Garcia-Saavedra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>5G-TRANSFORMER</title>
      <link>/project/transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/transformer/</guid>
      <description>5G-TRANSFORMER is an H2020 PPP project co-funded by the European Commission under the ICT theme (H2020-ICT-2016-2). 5G-TRANSFORMER aims to transform today’s mobile transport    network    into    an    SDN/NFV-based Mobile    Transport    and    Computing    Platform (MTP),    which    brings the  &amp;ldquo;Network  Slicing&amp;rdquo; paradigm   into   mobile   transport   networks   by provisioning and managing MTP slices tailored to the specific needs   of   vertical   industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5G-CROSSHAUL</title>
      <link>/project/crosshaul/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/crosshaul/</guid>
      <description>5G-Crosshaul is an H2020 PPP project co-funded by the European Commission under the ICT theme (Call 14). The 5G-Crosshaul project aims at developing a 5G integrated backhaul and fronthaul transport network enabling a flexible and software-defined reconfiguration of all networking elements in a multi-tenant and service-oriented unified management environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FLAVIA</title>
      <link>/project/flavia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/flavia/</guid>
      <description>FLAVIA is a project funded by the European Commission under FP7 Call 5, Objective 1.1: The Network of the Future. FLAVIA fosters a paradigm shift towards the Future Wireless Internet: from pre-designed link services to programmable link processors. The key concept is to expose flexible programmable interfaces enabling service customization and performance optimization through software-based exploitation of low-level operations and control primitives, e.g., transmission timing, frame customization and processing, spectrum and channel management, power control, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CARMEN</title>
      <link>/project/carmen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/carmen/</guid>
      <description>CARMEN (CARrier grade MEsh Networks) is funded by the European Commission under the ICT theme ICT-2007.1.1 - The network of the future. CARMEN will study and specify a wireless mesh network supporting carrier grade triple-play services for mobile/fixed network operators. Future operator networks will be comprised of a common core network and several access networks, and the CARMEN access network will complement other access technologies by providing a low cost and fast deployment mesh network access technology. The project proposes the integration of heterogeneous wireless technologies in a multi-hop fashion to provide scalable and efficient ubiquitous quad-play carrier services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>