<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>5G on Andres Garcia-Saavedra</title>
    <link>/tags/5g/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 5G on Andres Garcia-Saavedra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/5g/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>5Growth</title>
      <link>/project/5growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/5growth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;strong&gt;Role: Work Package (2) Leader.&lt;/strong&gt; The vision of the 5Growth project is to empower verticals industries such as Industry 4.0, Transportation, and Energy with an AI-driven Automated and Sharable 5G End-to-End Solution that will allow these industries to achieve simultaneously their respective key performance targets. Towards this vision, 5Growth will automate the process for supporting diverse industry verticals through (i) a vertical portal in charge of interfacing verticals with the 5G End-to-End platforms, receiving their service requests and building the respective network slices on top, (ii) closed-loop automation and SLA control for vertical services lifecycle management and (iii) AI-driven end-to-end network solutions to jointly optimize Access, Transport, Core and Cloud, Edge and Fog resources, across multiple technologies and domains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5G-TRANSFORMER</title>
      <link>/project/transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/transformer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;strong&gt;Role: Research Personnel.&lt;/strong&gt; 5G-TRANSFORMER aims to bring the “network slicing” paradigm to mobile transport networks by provisioning and managing such slices tailored to the specific needs of vertical industries, in particular automotive, healthcare, media and entertainment, and manufacturing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5G-CROSSHAUL</title>
      <link>/project/crosshaul/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/crosshaul/</guid>
      <description>&lt;strong&gt;Role: Research Personnel.&lt;/strong&gt; 5G-Crosshaul is an H2020 PPP project co-funded by the European Commission under the ICT theme (Call 14). The 5G-Crosshaul project aims at developing a 5G integrated backhaul and fronthaul transport network enabling a flexible and software-defined reconfiguration of all networking elements in a multi-tenant and service-oriented unified management environment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>