<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>network slicing on Andres Garcia-Saavedra</title>
    <link>/tags/network-slicing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in network slicing on Andres Garcia-Saavedra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/network-slicing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>5Growth</title>
      <link>/project/5growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/5growth/</guid>
      <description>The vision of the 5Growth project is to empower verticals industries such as Industry 4.0, Transportation, and Energy with an AI-driven Automated and Sharable 5G End-to-End Solution that will allow these industries to achieve simultaneously their respective key performance targets. Towards this vision, 5Growth will automate the process for supporting diverse industry verticals through (i) a vertical portal in charge of interfacing verticals with the 5G End-to-End platforms, receiving their service requests and building the respective network slices on top, (ii) closed-loop automation and SLA control for vertical services lifecycle management and (iii) AI-driven end-to-end network solutions to jointly optimize Access, Transport, Core and Cloud, Edge and Fog resources, across multiple technologies and domains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5G-TRANSFORMER</title>
      <link>/project/transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/transformer/</guid>
      <description>5G-TRANSFORMER is an H2020 PPP project co-funded by the European Commission under the ICT theme (H2020-ICT-2016-2). 5G-TRANSFORMER aims to transform today’s mobile transport    network    into    an    SDN/NFV-based Mobile    Transport    and    Computing    Platform (MTP),    which    brings the  &amp;ldquo;Network  Slicing&amp;rdquo; paradigm   into   mobile   transport   networks   by provisioning and managing MTP slices tailored to the specific needs   of   vertical   industries.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>